alexmalave.com 2016-03-07

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy:

Dynasty Media LLC (" **Alex Malave** ") operates alexmalave.com and may operate other websites. It is Alex Malave's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Alex Malave collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Alex Malave's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Alex Malave's visitors use its website. From time to time, Alex Malave may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Alex Malave also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on alexmalave.com blogs/sites. Alex Malave only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Alex Malave's websites choose to interact with Alex Malave in ways that require Alex Malave to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Alex Malave gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at [alexmalave.com](http://alexmalave.com/) to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Alex Malave are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Alex Malave collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Alex Malave. Alex Malave does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Alex Malave may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Alex Malave may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Alex Malave does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Alex Malave discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Alex Malave's behalf or to provide services available at Alex Malave's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Alex Malave's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Alex Malave will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Alex Malave discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Alex Malave believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Alex Malave, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Alex Malave website and have supplied your email address, Alex Malave may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Alex Malave and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Alex Malave takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Alex Malave uses cookies to help Alex Malave identify and track visitors, their usage of Alex Malave website, and their website access preferences. Alex Malave visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Alex Malave's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Alex Malave's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If Alex Malave, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Alex Malave goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Alex Malave may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Alex Malave and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Alex Malave may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Alex Malave's sole discretion. Alex Malave encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a alexmalave.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
